casetext.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy

### Privacy Policy

Effective: July 2, 2013 

Last updated: July 2, 2013 

We respect your privacy and consider protecting it a serious goal. In the course of using Casetext, you may provide us with personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you, with contributions to our website, and with information on your activities at our website. This privacy policy tells you how we collect, use, disclose, and protect your information; the policy applies to all of the products, services, and websites offered by J2H2, Inc., which owns and operates Casetext. You accept the terms and conditions of this privacy policy when you accept our Terms. 

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the “Last updated” date above. 

#### Information Collection and Use

We collect information that you provide or that is collected automatically when you use Casetext. 

We use that information in a number of ways: 

  * (a) to deliver the services you request,
  * (b) to improve our website, services, features, and content,
  * (c) to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate our website,
  * (d) to personalize your experience, including by using location-based information,
  * (e) to provide or offer updates and announcements,
  * (f) to provide you with further information and offers from us or third parties that we believe you may find useful or interesting, including newsletters, marketing, or promotional materials and other information on services and products offered by us or third parties,
  * (g) to monitor and analyze use of our website and our services,
  * (h) to administer our website,
  * (i) to generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics, and website use behavior of our users, and
  * (j) to verify that visitors to our website meet the criteria required to process their requests.

We reserve the right to compile and share aggregated information about our users, transactions completed using our service, sales, and traffic, though we will not share this information in a manner that permits the identification of a specific user without prior permission from that user. 

##### Content Provided by You

When you contribute to Casetext, the content you post and metadata about that content (such as the time you posted the content) will be viewable by the public, along with your name. This information will be searchable online and may be reused or modified elsewhere. Please see our Terms—particularly the section on  Subscriber Content—for more information. 

We may aggregate and display information about your publicly viewable activities on Casetext in your profile, which is also viewable by the public. For example, your profile may include a list of the tags, analysis, related materials, and other annotations that you have contributed. 

##### Other Information Provided by You

When you register for an account, add profile information, or purchase any product or service from us, you give us personal information. For example, we may collect and store your name, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email, and postal address. If you use a social networking website (such as Google+, LinkedIn, or Facebook) to sign in, we will also collect and store your user ID for that social network. 

Your name and the information you add to your profile will be viewable by the public. You can review or request changes to this information by logging into your account at [www.casetext.com](http://www.casetext.com/) or by contacting us at support@casroombaetext.com. 

We may contact you using the email you provide, and if you correspond with us by email, we may keep records of those email conversations. We will generally send you messages that relate to transactions you conduct on our website or that have important alerts and notices about your account or our services. You cannot opt out of these communications. Additionally, we may send you other communications such as (a) notices about your use of our services, including notices regarding violations of our terms of service, (b) updates to our website and services, and (c) promotional information regarding our services. You can opt out of receiving promotional emails by contacting us at unsubscroombaribe@casetext.com with your specific request. 

##### Information Collected Automatically

Cookies and web beacons are small files that enable us to capture and remember certain information. We use cookies and web beacons to enable certain features of our website, to understand and save your preferences for future visits, and to compile aggregate data about user traffic and behavior so that we can offer better experiences and tools in the future. We also may use other technologies for these purposes. 

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our website visitors. We may also allow third-party advertisers to serve advertisements on our website or otherwise tied to our services. These third parties may also use technologies like cookies to collect information, and we do not control their use of these technologies. You can configure your software so it does not accept cookies, though you may not be able to access certain portions or features of our website. 

#### Protection of Your Information

We take reasonable steps to maintain the safety of your information. However, we cannot guarantee that any confidential or personal information stored on our systems will be maintained at adequate levels of protection to meet specific needs or obligations you may have relating to that information, and we cannot guarantee that such information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by a breach of our safeguards. 

#### Disclosure to Third Parties

We may sell, transfer, or otherwise share your information to third parties or any data that you store using our services to a third party as outlined in this privacy policy, as required by law, or with your consent. We may share your information with trusted third parties that assist us in operating our website, conducting and improving our business, or providing services for you, in which case we will provide access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks. Additionally, we may sell, transfer, or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including your information, in connection with a corporate transaction such as a merger, acquisition, reorganization, or sale of assets. In any such event, you will receive notice if your data is transferred and becomes subject to a substantially different privacy policy. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our policies, or protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. Non-personally identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

#### Third-Party Services

Third-party websites that are linked to our website are not controlled by us, and we are not responsible for their policies or content. Your interactions with such websites are governed only by the terms and conditions and privacy policies of those websites. 

We may link to, include, or offer third-party products or services on or through our website. If you choose to use any such third-party services, we may facilitate sharing of your information and documents you choose to use with those services. Your use of those services is not governed by our Terms or this privacy policy. We do not control the services of those third parties or how they use your information and documents. Be sure to review the terms and conditions and privacy policies of those third parties before using their services. 

#### Terms of Use

Please see our Terms for further information on the rules, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of Casetext and its services. 

#### California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, you may obtain a list of any third parties to whom we have disclosed your personally identifiable information for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the types of personally identifiable information disclosed to them. You may request such a list once a year by emailing policiroombaes@casetext.com, and you will receive it at no cost. 

#### Questions?

Contact us at poroombalicies@casetext.com if you have any questions about this privacy policy. 

#### Recent Updates

There are no recent updates to this privacy policy.
